WENDY WIGG

(503) 808-0671 | wiggwendy@gmail.com | github.com/wneek018 | linkedin.com/in/wiggwendy

Professional Summary

Detail-oriented Full Stack Web Developer with a background in Accounting. Recently graduated with a Certificate from the University of Washington's Full Stack Web Development program. Quick learner with experience in creating secure user authentication in full-stack applications with JavaScript, Passport.js, MongoDB, MySQL and Node.js. Motivated to become a Full Stack Web Developer that maintains and creates apps that make people's lives easier.

Projects

Tastes & Tunes - group project inspired by the home event planner. In this project we linked the YouTube and Spoonacular APIs to generate playlists based on a type of cuisine.

Taskmaster3000 - a personal ToDo list. Created using Node.js, Express, MySQL, Passport.js and deployed to Heroku. https://uwproject2.herokuapp.com/

SayWhaaaat? - multiplayer React game using Socket.io, Passport.js, Mongoose, MongoDB, Express, and Node.js. Deployed to Heroku. https://uw-bootcamp-project3.herokuapp.com/

Work Experience

Genoa Healthcare - subsidiary of OptumRx, division of UnitedHealth Group

Jun 2018 - Apr 2019

Lease Accountant

- Successfully developed new lease process with adoption of standard ASC 842
- Facilitated lease adjustments both internally and externally with OptumRx acquisition

Placed, Inc. - subsidiary of Snap, Inc

Jan 2016 - Jun 2018

Revenue Accountant

- Reconcile revenue at month end and post accrual journal entries
- Coordinate extensively with internal auditors for month and year end close

The Equitable Finance Company

Aug 2014 - Dec 2015

Staff Accountant

Maintained 50+ investor GL accounts, prepped month end close and reports for annual audit

Education

University of Washington - Seattle, WA

Certificate, Full Stack Web Development

Feb 2019 - Present

Gonzaga University - Spokane, WA

May 2014

Bachelor of Business Administration, Accounting Gonzaga Women's Rowing team

Aug 2010 - May 2014